(Amy:)I don't think that was
the point of the movie.
(Sheldon:)Fine, then I was like Pinocchio
(Sheldon:)before that jerk Geppetto
went and made him a real boy.
(Amy:)There you go.
(Penny:)So, what are you
thinking for dinner?
(Leonard:)Well, it's Thai food night.
(Penny:)Well, honey,
(Penny:)you don't live
with Sheldon anymore.
(Penny:)You can have anything you want.
(Leonard:)You're right.
(Leonard:)But what?
(Leonard:)Mexican?
(Leonard:)Italian? German?
(Leonard:)Indian? Greek?
(Leonard:)Cuban? Chinese?
(Leonard:)Pizza? Barbecue?
(Leonard:)Korean? Korean barbecue?
(Penny:)How about Thai food?
(Leonard:)Oh, thank God.
(Penny:)Hey, we're going to dinner.
You want to come?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I wish I could,
(Sheldon:)but I realized I've become
too emotionally vulnerable,
(Sheldon:)so, like an operating system,
(Sheldon:)I'm restoring my life
to the last stable version,
(Sheldon:)which was in 2003,
the day before I met Leonard.
(Leonard:)You heard him, no.